[
    {
        "task_id": 1,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (-2 - 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "4",
        "wrong_answer2": "3",
        "wrong_answer3": "5",
        "correct_answer": "2",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 2,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -4i \\cdot (-1 + i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "3",
        "wrong_answer2": "1",
        "wrong_answer3": "6",
        "correct_answer": "4",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 3,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 4i \\cdot (1 - 8 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "1",
        "wrong_answer2": "2",
        "wrong_answer3": "7",
        "correct_answer": "4",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 4,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 1i \\cdot (1 - 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-1",
        "wrong_answer2": "-2",
        "wrong_answer3": "4",
        "correct_answer": "1",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 5,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 4i \\cdot (5 - 4 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "17",
        "wrong_answer2": "19",
        "wrong_answer3": "23",
        "correct_answer": "20",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 6,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -5i \\cdot (-6 + 8 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "27",
        "wrong_answer2": "29",
        "wrong_answer3": "33",
        "correct_answer": "30",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 7,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (-1 + 2 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-2",
        "wrong_answer2": "0",
        "wrong_answer3": "-4",
        "correct_answer": "-3",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 8,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 5i \\cdot (-1 - 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-4",
        "wrong_answer2": "-3",
        "wrong_answer3": "-8",
        "correct_answer": "-5",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 9,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 4i \\cdot (-7 + 7 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-27",
        "wrong_answer2": "-30",
        "wrong_answer3": "-25",
        "correct_answer": "-28",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 10,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (3 + 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-1",
        "wrong_answer2": "-5",
        "wrong_answer3": "-6",
        "correct_answer": "-3",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 11,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 1i \\cdot (-3 - 5 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "0",
        "wrong_answer2": "-4",
        "wrong_answer3": "-5",
        "correct_answer": "-3",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 12,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 9i \\cdot (-4 + 8 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-34",
        "wrong_answer2": "-39",
        "wrong_answer3": "-33",
        "correct_answer": "-36",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 13,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (3 + i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-2",
        "wrong_answer2": "0",
        "wrong_answer3": "-4",
        "correct_answer": "-3",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 14,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 4i \\cdot (-3 - 4 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-11",
        "wrong_answer2": "-10",
        "wrong_answer3": "-14",
        "correct_answer": "-12",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 15,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (8 + 6 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "17",
        "wrong_answer2": "15",
        "wrong_answer3": "18",
        "correct_answer": "16",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 16,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (-2 + 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-3",
        "wrong_answer2": "-5",
        "wrong_answer3": "-2",
        "correct_answer": "-4",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 17,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (-5 - 2 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-8",
        "wrong_answer2": "-9",
        "wrong_answer3": "-7",
        "correct_answer": "-10",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 18,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 10i \\cdot (5 - 4 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "47",
        "wrong_answer2": "49",
        "wrong_answer3": "52",
        "correct_answer": "50",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 19,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (-2 + 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-1",
        "wrong_answer2": "-5",
        "wrong_answer3": "-3",
        "correct_answer": "-4",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 20,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (-5 - 5 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-13",
        "wrong_answer2": "-7",
        "wrong_answer3": "-12",
        "correct_answer": "-10",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 21,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -7i \\cdot (2 - i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-16",
        "wrong_answer2": "-12",
        "wrong_answer3": "-17",
        "correct_answer": "-14",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 22,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (1 + 2 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-1",
        "wrong_answer2": "0",
        "wrong_answer3": "1",
        "correct_answer": "2",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 23,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 5i \\cdot (-1 - 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-8",
        "wrong_answer2": "-3",
        "wrong_answer3": "-6",
        "correct_answer": "-5",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 24,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -2i \\cdot (3 + 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-5",
        "wrong_answer2": "-8",
        "wrong_answer3": "-9",
        "correct_answer": "-6",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 25,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -3i \\cdot (3 + 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-12",
        "wrong_answer2": "-8",
        "wrong_answer3": "-6",
        "correct_answer": "-9",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 26,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (4 - 4 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-6",
        "wrong_answer2": "-7",
        "wrong_answer3": "-3",
        "correct_answer": "-4",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 27,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 1i \\cdot (5 - 8 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "3",
        "wrong_answer2": "8",
        "wrong_answer3": "6",
        "correct_answer": "5",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 28,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 1i \\cdot (-1 + 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "1",
        "wrong_answer2": "-4",
        "wrong_answer3": "2",
        "correct_answer": "-1",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 29,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (-1 - 4 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "3",
        "wrong_answer2": "-2",
        "wrong_answer3": "-1",
        "correct_answer": "1",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 30,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -7i \\cdot (-8 - 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "59",
        "wrong_answer2": "55",
        "wrong_answer3": "53",
        "correct_answer": "56",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 31,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -2i \\cdot (2 + 2 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-1",
        "wrong_answer2": "-3",
        "wrong_answer3": "-7",
        "correct_answer": "-4",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 32,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -3i \\cdot (-1 - 4 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "5",
        "wrong_answer2": "1",
        "wrong_answer3": "0",
        "correct_answer": "3",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 33,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 7i \\cdot (4 + 9 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "27",
        "wrong_answer2": "31",
        "wrong_answer3": "25",
        "correct_answer": "28",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 34,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (3 - 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "8",
        "wrong_answer2": "6",
        "wrong_answer3": "7",
        "correct_answer": "9",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 35,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (3 + 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "0",
        "wrong_answer2": "-6",
        "wrong_answer3": "-2",
        "correct_answer": "-3",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 36,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 10i \\cdot (-1 + 4 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-9",
        "wrong_answer2": "-11",
        "wrong_answer3": "-13",
        "correct_answer": "-10",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 37,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -3i \\cdot (2 - 2 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-5",
        "wrong_answer2": "-4",
        "wrong_answer3": "-3",
        "correct_answer": "-6",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 38,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (1 + 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "0",
        "wrong_answer2": "1",
        "wrong_answer3": "6",
        "correct_answer": "3",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 39,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (-8 + i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-22",
        "wrong_answer2": "-23",
        "wrong_answer3": "-26",
        "correct_answer": "-24",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 40,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -3i \\cdot (-1 - 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "5",
        "wrong_answer2": "1",
        "wrong_answer3": "4",
        "correct_answer": "3",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 41,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -5i \\cdot (-2 + 2 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "8",
        "wrong_answer2": "7",
        "wrong_answer3": "11",
        "correct_answer": "10",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 42,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -3i \\cdot (-5 + 10 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "17",
        "wrong_answer2": "13",
        "wrong_answer3": "16",
        "correct_answer": "15",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 43,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (3 - 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "12",
        "wrong_answer2": "10",
        "wrong_answer3": "11",
        "correct_answer": "9",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 44,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 4i \\cdot (2 - 2 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "11",
        "wrong_answer2": "7",
        "wrong_answer3": "5",
        "correct_answer": "8",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 45,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -4i \\cdot (5 + 5 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-22",
        "wrong_answer2": "-18",
        "wrong_answer3": "-19",
        "correct_answer": "-20",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 46,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (-3 + 2 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-8",
        "wrong_answer2": "-10",
        "wrong_answer3": "-11",
        "correct_answer": "-9",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 47,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (-1 + 5 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "0",
        "wrong_answer2": "-5",
        "wrong_answer3": "-6",
        "correct_answer": "-3",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 48,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 6i \\cdot (-4 - 5 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-21",
        "wrong_answer2": "-23",
        "wrong_answer3": "-27",
        "correct_answer": "-24",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 49,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (2 - 2 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "7",
        "wrong_answer2": "4",
        "wrong_answer3": "9",
        "correct_answer": "6",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 50,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -5i \\cdot (4 - 2 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-17",
        "wrong_answer2": "-18",
        "wrong_answer3": "-19",
        "correct_answer": "-20",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 51,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -5i \\cdot (2 + 7 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-12",
        "wrong_answer2": "-7",
        "wrong_answer3": "-9",
        "correct_answer": "-10",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 52,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (-1 - 2 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "4",
        "wrong_answer2": "2",
        "wrong_answer3": "-2",
        "correct_answer": "1",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 53,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -5i \\cdot (-1 + i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "4",
        "wrong_answer2": "2",
        "wrong_answer3": "3",
        "correct_answer": "5",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 54,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -9i \\cdot (2 + 8 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-15",
        "wrong_answer2": "-19",
        "wrong_answer3": "-17",
        "correct_answer": "-18",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 55,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -2i \\cdot (3 + 2 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-9",
        "wrong_answer2": "-7",
        "wrong_answer3": "-3",
        "correct_answer": "-6",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 56,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (-2 + i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "4",
        "wrong_answer2": "1",
        "wrong_answer3": "5",
        "correct_answer": "2",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 57,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 9i \\cdot (-10 - 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-89",
        "wrong_answer2": "-93",
        "wrong_answer3": "-91",
        "correct_answer": "-90",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 58,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (-2 - 3 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-3",
        "wrong_answer2": "-2",
        "wrong_answer3": "-6",
        "correct_answer": "-4",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 59,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -3i \\cdot (2 - 5 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-7",
        "wrong_answer2": "-8",
        "wrong_answer3": "-3",
        "correct_answer": "-6",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 60,
        "question": "\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -4i \\cdot (-1 + 10 i)?",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "6",
        "wrong_answer2": "1",
        "wrong_answer3": "2",
        "correct_answer": "4",
        "topic": "c",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 61,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 2x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 62,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 3 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 6 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 6x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 6 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 6 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 63,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 6 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "12x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 64,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 2x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 65,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 3 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 6 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 6 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 6x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 6 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 66,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 4 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 8x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 67,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 2x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 68,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 2 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 4 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 4 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 4x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 4 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 69,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 5 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 10x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 70,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\sin{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 3 x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 3 x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 3x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 3 x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 71,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 2x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 72,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 4 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 8x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 73,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "2x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 74,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 3 \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 6 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 6 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 6x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 6 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 75,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 4 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "8x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 76,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "3x^{2} \\sin{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "3 x^{2} \\sin{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "3 x^{2} \\sin{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "3 x^{2} \\sin{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 77,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 2 \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "4 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "4 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "4x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "4 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 78,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 4 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "8x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 79,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "2x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 80,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 2x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 81,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 6 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "12x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 82,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "2x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 83,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 2 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "4x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "4 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "4 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "4 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 84,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 5 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 10x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 85,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\sin{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "3 x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "3x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "3 x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "3 x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 86,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "2x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 87,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 5 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "10x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 88,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 2x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 89,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 3 \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 6 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 6 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 6 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 6x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 90,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 6 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "12x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 91,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "2x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 92,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 3 \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 6 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 6 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 6x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 6 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 93,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 5 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "10x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 94,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "2x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 95,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 2 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "4 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "4 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "4x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "4 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 96,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 4 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 8x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 97,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 2x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 98,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 3 \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 6x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 6 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 6 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 6 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 99,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 4 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 8x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 100,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\sin{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 3x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 3 x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 3 x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 3 x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 101,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "2x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 102,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 5 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "10x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 103,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\sin{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "3 x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "3 x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "3 x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "3x^{2} \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 104,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "2x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 105,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 5 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 10x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 106,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\cos{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "3 x^{2} \\sin{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "3 x^{2} \\sin{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "3x^{2} \\sin{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "3 x^{2} \\sin{\\left(x^{3} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 107,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 2x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 108,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 5 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 10 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 10x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 109,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "2x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 110,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 2 \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 4x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 4 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 4 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 4 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 111,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 6 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "12x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 112,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "2x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 113,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 3 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 6x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 6 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 6 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 6 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 114,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 4 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "8x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 115,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 2x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 116,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 2x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 2 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 117,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - 6 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "12x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "12 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 118,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = - \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 2x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 119,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "2x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "2 x \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 120,
        "question": "Given the function f(x) = 4 \\cos{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "answer_stub": "What is f'(x)?",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 8 x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "correct_answer": "- 8x \\sin{\\left(x^{2} \\right)}",
        "topic": "d",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 121,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\pi\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "360^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-67.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "157.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-180^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 122,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{7 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-247.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-225^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "-360^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-157.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 123,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-382.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-315^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "67.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "135^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 124,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\pi\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "270^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "135^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "-360^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-180^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 125,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{7 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-337.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-360^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "202.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-157.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 126,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{11 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "67.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-337.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "-157.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-247.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 127,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{\\pi}{2}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "180^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-382.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "-270^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "90^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 128,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{3 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "90^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-22.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "-337.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-67.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 129,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{9 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "67.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "337.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "315^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "202.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 130,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{\\pi}{2}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-180^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "225^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "202.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-90^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 131,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "337.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "157.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "292.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-112.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 132,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{15 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "315^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-157.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "90^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-337.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 133,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{\\pi}{2}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-202.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "67.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "-247.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-90^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 134,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "247.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-90^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "157.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "112.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 135,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "180^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-45^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "-90^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "337.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 136,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-135^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-67.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "360^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "135^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 137,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "360^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "270^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "-135^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "112.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 138,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{3 \\pi}{2}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-112.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "90^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "292.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "270^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 139,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\pi\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-45^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "315^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "270^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "180^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 140,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "270^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-292.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "292.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "112.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 141,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "225^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-180^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "270^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "337.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 142,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "292.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-202.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "-135^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "135^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 143,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{\\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-112.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-382.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "225^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-22.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 144,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{3 \\pi}{2}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "22.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-135^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "247.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-270^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 145,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\pi\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "135^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-247.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "337.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-180^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 146,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{\\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-382.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-180^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "-135^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "22.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 147,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{11 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "45^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-315^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "247.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "-247.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 148,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{\\pi}{2}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-180^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-202.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "270^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "90^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 149,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{\\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "-180^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "67.5^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "-247.5^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "22.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 150,
        "question": "\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "360^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer2": "-225^\\circ",
        "wrong_answer3": "-45^\\circ",
        "correct_answer": "337.5^\\circ",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 151,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }45^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{9 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\pi",
        "correct_answer": "\\frac{\\pi}{4}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 152,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-112.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\pi",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\frac{\\pi}{2}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 153,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }337.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{13 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{3 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 154,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-45^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{7 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{13 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\frac{7 \\pi}{4}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{\\pi}{4}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 155,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-22.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\frac{9 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\frac{3 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\frac{\\pi}{4}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{\\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 156,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-337.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\frac{9 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\frac{7 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\frac{13 \\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{15 \\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 157,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }90^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{3 \\pi}{2}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\frac{\\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "\\frac{\\pi}{2}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 158,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }157.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{15 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\frac{11 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\frac{7 \\pi}{4}",
        "correct_answer": "\\frac{7 \\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 159,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-315^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\frac{7 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{\\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{3 \\pi}{4}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{7 \\pi}{4}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 160,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-90^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{15 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{3 \\pi}{2}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\frac{11 \\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{\\pi}{2}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 161,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-67.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\pi",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\frac{\\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{9 \\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{3 \\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 162,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-67.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{5 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\frac{9 \\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{3 \\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 163,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }135^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- 2 \\pi",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{5 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{\\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 164,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-67.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{17 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\pi",
        "wrong_answer3": "2 \\pi",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{3 \\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 165,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-22.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{\\pi}{2}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{3 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{3 \\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{\\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 166,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }45^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\frac{3 \\pi}{2}",
        "correct_answer": "\\frac{\\pi}{4}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 167,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-22.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{9 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\frac{15 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\frac{9 \\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{\\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 168,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }315^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\frac{7 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\frac{5 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{3 \\pi}{4}",
        "correct_answer": "\\frac{7 \\pi}{4}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 169,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-180^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\frac{\\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{3 \\pi}{4}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\pi",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 170,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-112.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "2 \\pi",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{7 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{3 \\pi}{2}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 171,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }90^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\pi",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{\\pi}{4}",
        "correct_answer": "\\frac{\\pi}{2}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 172,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-90^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{5 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\pi",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{\\pi}{2}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 173,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-157.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\frac{5 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\frac{11 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\frac{13 \\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{7 \\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 174,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-135^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\frac{7 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\pi",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{7 \\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{3 \\pi}{4}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 175,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }135^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "- \\frac{11 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- 2 \\pi",
        "correct_answer": "\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 176,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-157.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\frac{5 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{\\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "\\pi",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{7 \\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 177,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }247.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{3 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{5 \\pi}{4}",
        "correct_answer": "\\frac{11 \\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 178,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }90^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{7 \\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{\\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{\\pi}{2}",
        "correct_answer": "\\frac{\\pi}{2}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 179,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }22.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{7 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{\\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "\\frac{\\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    },
    {
        "task_id": 180,
        "question": "\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-337.5^\\circ\\text{?}",
        "answer_stub": "",
        "wrong_answer1": "- \\frac{\\pi}{4}",
        "wrong_answer2": "\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}",
        "wrong_answer3": "- \\frac{11 \\pi}{8}",
        "correct_answer": "- \\frac{15 \\pi}{8}",
        "topic": "r",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": "10",
        "status": "a",
        "user_id": 60
    }
]